I will kill you today.
You will die at my sword.
What's up?
Someone's writing Arabic.
I don't know what it means.
I can't read that.
Also, I'm pretty sure you read that backwards, right?
Isaac!
Are you ready for Isaac?
We're gonna jam the eye all the way into the sack.
Today.
You're perpetually three vods behind.
Thanks for the sub, you jury.
It's okay, you can skip a couple vods.
Thank you, it's car.
100% demon mode.
Oh, you know it.
Except not really, actually.
Today, we're going angel.
I'm feeling angel today.
We gotta do angel.
I do very little angel, and I've been burned by the demons lately.
Every time I touch them, it's like, ah!
Ah!
That's hot, you know?
It's too much.
It hurts.
You say that every time.
You know?
Okay, yeah, you're right.
But today, for real though, we're going angel.
Not a single demon today.
Only angel.
Oh yeah.
Please no Beth.
Oh, you got it.
I'm not gonna do Beth.
Don't worry about that.
It's okay.
Okay.
Oh, I need to switch your room.
Wow, isn't this song great?
Makes me want to play Red Alert 2.
That's right, you heard me.
Oh yeah.
Actually, right now, makes me want to play this.
Because now I heard the Isaac song.
It's calling.
Guys, I have decided that the random is broken in this game.
So we're not gonna do that anymore.
I am gonna choose what I want to play.
And I think we gotta go with an Isaac.
We saw first-hand last time what random does.
It ain't pretty.
There's no random is there.
Not at all.
It's very weighted.
It's a weighted dice.
We're gonna go Isaac.
Or maybe even Judas.
Because we don't have any of those red things on Judas at all.
Sam's on as bloody as hell.
Okay, never mind.
This Hazel is pretty bloody.
You know what?
Eulith.
I don't think I've ever played Eulith outside of Greed.
I'm thinking Eulith, actually.
Let's start with that.
I like it.
Also, today is the first day of this year where it's so hot in here, that it may actually become a fever dream stream.
Just warning you beforehand, okay?
Now you're warned.
It's pretty bad.
It's really, really hot.
Wait, how does that work for me?
That doesn't work for me, does it?
It does!
Wait, what?
Oh, it's my familiar shooting it.
Ah.
That is either pretty good or pretty bad.
Okay, it's pretty good.
Oh, what?
It causes all...
Picking up a HP up food item, grant two small permanent stat ingredients.
Dude, what the fuck?
What a start!
I mean, this is pretty damn good.
Can't really complain there.
There we go.
I'm a little bit scared though of the bomb, you know?
Because the bomb can hurt me and it's not being shot from me.
Things can go wrong here.
It's getting a little awkward.
Dude, will you please die?
There we go.
Now, obviously, I gotta destroy all the rocks.
Hold on, I gotta adjust my seating position.
Because we are gonna find crawl spaces.
That's right, we're going to space.
Dude, I'm not comfortable with my current seating configuration.
Hold on.
Uh, maybe like that.
Uh, okay.
Whoa!
How did you not die?
Okay, there we go.
I'm playing it safe.
There's no reason to go crazy here.
Epikak is kind of nuts.
Dude, imagine if I get more familiars.
They're gonna shoot twice Epikak and three times Epikak.
It's gonna be crazy.
Now, here I gotta be a little careful because I don't want to accidentally destroy that.
Okay, good.
All right, so these are gonna alternate between HP.
This could be a step run, just because of that.
I also want to destroy this guy, actually.
There we go.
Thank you.
Play it safe.
I mean, this run is gonna go hard.
I really have to fuck this up, guys, to mess it up, okay?
We're gonna try not to do that.
The secrets.
Well, there we go.
Oh my god, we got money now.
All the money.
Holy shit.
What was that one?
I mean, damage for me doesn't matter, really, right?
That's useless.
This one is luck.
I like luck on that one.
And what else is it?
One health.
I guess I can pause the game.
That's probably easier.
Vengeful Racer.
And this one was healing damage to enemies, gradually recharges, right?
Dude, this is gonna recharge so fast.
Whoa.
Dude, my Epikak is gonna make this go hard, right?
I kind of want to take that.
I'm doing it.
Fuck it.
I have a feeling it's gonna be great.
Now I just gotta remember to use my active, but not here.
Like, right here is fuck.
A waste, right?
Get away from me.
It's a little bit awkward to... Oh, can I?
No.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh god.
It's always awkward in the beginning with Epikak.
There we go.
I'm trying here.
Nice.
Show me the crawl space.
I need it.
Uh,
it's Steven.
Duplication.
Wow.
Holy shit.
Dude, I can say no to Steven.
That's so awesome.
But wait, maybe I want Steven.
Is he gonna shoot Epikaks?
Let's try.
He's not.
Okay.
Now I regret it.
But it's okay.
He's still gonna be duplicated, right?
So my active is still kind of cool.
From now on, we're gonna focus on HP items.
The cool thing is we can always get HP items now.
Because we got the Mega Breakfast or whatever.
Destroy everything.
Uh, I'm a little scared here.
I gotta destroy everything, right?
Uh, walking in here...
Uh,
it, uh, no.
No, no, no, no.
We're not doing it.
Even though it could be the money we need for the shop.
Nice.
Okay.
Well, at least we tried it.
I mean, I could go in here and... You know what?
We're doing it.
This is gonna be the run to really own.
We need to own this run.
It needs to happen.
I'm taking the midnight snack, baby.
Yeah, I'm doing it.
I'm doing it.
We're gonna go in here.
You think I'm afraid?
I'm not.
Not when I have Epikak.
Epikak shall rule everything.
You'll see.
It's gonna be good.
Yeah!
Oh, that was a little bit scary.
Oh, god.
Okay, good.
So, let's see what we got here.
Bob's Brain.
It's a familiar that charges, explodes and applies poison.
I mean, I think every familiar I get is good.
And this is gonna take me to two out of three on Bob, whatever that means.
Could be cool to experiment with.
Then we have this thing that gives me shot speed, doesn't matter.
Range doesn't matter.
Health does matter.
But I think we can afford to take one more familiar here.
We can always get more health later, right?
This is the thing.
Oh, we should be checking everything for the secrets.
Good.
10 Buckerinos.
Oh, it's so cheap!
Oh, my god.
We gotta take it.
That's awesome.
Could even buy a key if we want to.
Dude, how do I...
Can we blow this guy up, maybe?
Maybe if I walk like this.
I can't hit him.
Oh, wrong way.
Oh, shit.
I have too much range.
That's kind of crazy, isn't it?
Whatever.
Look for secrets.
Oh, the little green guy is like following my attack.
So that's how that works.
Blow them up.
Dude, I can't believe I don't have enough range to actually hit these guys.
That's crazy.
It is physically impossible for me to do it.
I have to use a bomb.
We need less range.
Wow.
Careful.
Okay, the little green guy is not getting duplicated by my active for some reason.
That's sad.
Shit.
Nice.
Oh,
destroy everything.
There's money in there.
Still no secrets found.
Never mind.
Oi, we're going to save that until the end.
I guess it's time for the boss.
Wormwood, but why is he colored like that?
Something's off.
Wait, wait, speedball?
Use this for me.
Another mid... Wait, two midnight snacks?
You can actually have two of the same item.
I think that's the first time I've ever had that.
Okay, we're not going to go inside the demon room.
Because we are going full angel.
I am going to go step though.
Just a little bit.
One more.
What?
Really?
Okay, fine.
Give me that.
I'm going to get the other heart down here.
I really thought I would get something for at least three steps.
We got a half a heart as well.
And then we're going to move on.
There we go.
Fuck, I fucked.
Got the fucking heart.
I swear to God, dude.
What is wrong with me?
Why does this happen?
Only to me.
Insanity.
I forgot the eternal heart.
That's fine.
It's going to be okay.
Don't despair.
Right.
The hermit.
Yeah, actually.
Another... Oh my God, another midnight snack.
There is such a thing as too much midnight snack, you know?
You're going to get fat if you keep eating at midnight.
I'm actually not going to do the fire thing.
I have other plans this run.
Yeah, I'm just here for fun.
That's it.
Now that one.
Oh, come on.
Good.
Yeah.
Blow him up.
Oh God.
I was a little too close there.
We should do the boss now while we still have a little buffer.
It's going to be close.
We may get hit here.
Turlet.
Whoa, nice.
Let's see here.
One black heart, three bombs.
I don't like that.
We take dinner.
We take it.
Another midnight snack.
Holy grail is also one health.
Kratz flight!
Yo!
Obviously, I take that.
We're going to save this.
No, wait.
We're not going to save this one.
Because I can't get back in here.
So hold on.
We're going to destroy these first, and then we're going to actually kill the angel.
Really?
Okay.
Nice.
Oh my God, we get... everything gets turned into hell.
Wait, do I even want this key piece?
Let me think.
Do we even want that?
What's that even going to do for me?
It's going to create the key and allow me to...
You know what?
Yeah, take it.
No, no.
Take the meat.
Fuck the key piece.
The plan is we're going to go... the plan is to get a teleport.
And then we go to mom and we teleport out of there.
This is the plan.
We're not done on this floor, though.
Careful.
There we go.
Dude, I need to reduce my range.
I got to eat pills.
Bad pills.
What's that?
Oh!
What happened?
Dinner?
Chocolate milk.
Places tears with a charge.
I don't like that.
I like my current one.
But honestly, I don't like dinner that much.
I'm going to go for the question mark.
It's breakfast.
Oh, it's more range.
No.
Shit.
It could have been good, you know?
Okay.
We also got to look for secrets.
The only way I'm going to hit enemies now is to hit them straight on, you know?
Why is that not blowing up?
What?
What's happening?
Okay, that was weird.
Range is too much.
I'm kind of scared to lose this eternal heart here.
Blow it up!
No!
That was a mistake.
I immediately recognized I would lose luck.
It was a mistake.
I fucked it up, guys.
You know what happened in my mind?
I saw a mirror and I was like, mirror bad!
Mirror makes me die.
So I was like, kill, kill!
I saw red, you know?
I had to kill it.
And then immediately after I shot, I realized my mistake.
It happens.
Dude, I need to eat pills.
I need pills in my system, man.
So bad.
Where are the secrets?
It
could be over here, actually.
Okay, well, that's kind of useless for me.
Dude, coupon!
It's kind of nice, but maybe not that nice for me.
Hold on.
Let me check the shop again.
I'll take this.
I'm going to take the other HP.
We're going to just go full HP here.
At this point, man, we'll do it, right?
Look for the last secret.
Okay, we got to buy this pill.
Oh, I don't have enough money.
I need to reduce my range.
Child leash.
Familius, follow more closely!
That could be good for me.
That's kind of nice, actually.
Okay, it's not that close, but it's good.
It's good.
They also get more damage.
That's like 25% more damage for the explosion, I guess.
That's crazy.
We're leaving now.
We're done here.
You know what?
Just go down here.
I feel like the other place is too risky for what I'm trying to do.
We got to find a teleport, though.
Yeah.
All right.
No buffer.
We're probably going to lose our angel shot here, but it is what it is.
Did we check everything?
No, we did.
Also, I can fly now.
I have to remember that.
Okay, this is not going to happen.
Can I really not hit that?
Okay.
You know what?
It's kind of nice having the followers shoot the bomb sometimes.
This means I can shoot them close range, and I won't take damage sometimes.
Okay, come on, please.
Range down.
Okay.
Damn.
The fruitcake.
No, I don't like that.
I mean, we're just going to go... Here's the thing, though.
I don't actually want more HP.
I don't know what this is going to do to my bombs.
Oh, it actually does affect it.
Oh, that's kind of cool.
I shouldn't have gone in here.
I'm going to lose my angel.
Crap.
I done goofed.
Oh, nevermind.
So wait, that doesn't affect it.
That's kind of huge.
Huh.
Well, there we go.
I don't know if I like the fruitcake.
It's making it very unpredictable, and I can sometimes hit myself with it.
Fruitcake was a mistake.
Yeah, you see that?
I'm just hitting myself here.
Dude, I have too much range.
Oh, my God, really.
I can't even destroy these rocks.
Okay, there we go.
Aha.
Ah, wait, I can fly.
Do we go full crazy with the mushroom?
No, no, I need the leash.
Keep them close.
The build looks good on paper right now, but it's really difficult to play because I have so much range.
It's kind of a tough one.
It doesn't feel good, you know?
Damn it.
Hey, a card.
Damn.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, oh, wait, we're doing demon.
Maybe I'll do demon.
No, I don't actually like any of this.
I don't like it.
The thing is, though, dude, we can do crazy demons because I can keep getting HP, right?
We can just go crazy here.
Right?
Hold on, this is like the demon run.
I know I said I didn't want to do demon, but how can I not with this?
Okay, I'm gonna lose a little bit of speed, but I'm gonna get my HP back, I guess, after I lose it.
Wait, what?
Oh, wait, I get more range.
I don't like that.
Take this.
Well, that didn't make sense, actually.
Maybe it's better to... Hold on, what happens if I do this now?
Oh, I like that, actually.
Maybe I say fuck the box of friends.
Because this is gonna bomb still, you know?
This is a good bomb.
Ooh.
Wait, this one is a chance for tears to apply.
That's also good.
Increases with luck, not so good.
Plus one health, plus one luck.
Okay, plus one.
Maybe that one, we take the midnight snack, get it back.
Yeah.
And then we do false PhD, I guess.
Because then we turn into bad pills, and we get to identify them.
We can reduce our range.
But that's not that good.
What's the other one?
That's more range.
Ew, I don't like that.
Hmm.
Well, you know what I need?
I need the one that makes me immune to explosions, because this is the only thing that's limiting me.
If I get that, I can easily use box of friends, stand in the corner, and go crazy, right?
This is what I'm afraid of right now.
That's why I'm drawn to this brimstone.
I didn't mean to take that one!
It switched on me last moment.
I'm gonna stick to my box.
Oh wait, I still have this effect, though.
Ah, you know what?
At least we got one out of three on Leviathan, I guess.
But whatever that's worth.
Where am I?
There.
Did you see that trajectory just now?
That was weird.
What's this room?
Yeah, I need pyromaniacs.
They're so unpredictable, these bombs.
Dude, I don't goof.
I don't understand how that path works there.
It's very confusing.
The devil, not what I need.
I mean, if I don't get a teleport card, then nothing is gonna matter.
Load this up.
It's time for polycephalus.
Polycephalus dead.
You know what?
I'll take the glass eye for the look.
Why not?
May as well do it.
Yeah, that one came back.
You saw that?
Scary.
Uh, so we found that secret room.
Gonna scan the entire area here.
That mushroom.
I'm gonna blow it up manually.
Ohoy!
Spawns a friendly spider for each enemy in the room?
Okay.
May as well do it.
Wow.
We got some mushrooms in here.
That's pretty cool.
I like that.
Oh, okay, that one.
God, I hate having this range.
Whoops.
Destroy these now.
Look at the way it came back!
Fucking hell.
Reminds me of those septic tanks from, uh, God, what's that?
Noiter.
No, the ones that go flailing all around.
Scary stuff.
Secret.
Hourglass.
Ooh, actually.
But, uh, I mean, I kind of like my box of friends.
It really is amplifying my damage like crazy, right?
Well, 2x is what it's doing, but...
And I also multiply all my other familiars, so I think it's worth it to keep.
Guess we'll take this and get locked back.
Yeah, why not?
This is such a weird run.
This is what I love about this game.
You know?
Like, what even is this right now?
I don't know, but it's awesome.
Nice.
Oh!
Oh, you bastard.
I mean, actually, I kind of like that.
Slow it down a bit.
It's too damn fast.
That one had a weird electricity effect on it.
I can't hit the man.
On the pill.
Shot speed down.
Okay, blow it up manually.
Still no teleport.
Not looking good.
I don't want that.
What a shot.
I think we're pretty much done here.
Maybe we do a fight room if we can.
We can't.
Okay, this floor is officially Duncease.
Let's move on.
Still no teleport card.
We could destroy this.
Whoa, I came back.
Why is that not getting destroyed?
What the fuck?
That's a funny effect.
Come on.
Yeah.
Nothing though, unfortunately.
Keep going.
Floor five.
This one is a doozy.
Ah, go north first.
Fuck!
Well, that was a mistake.
This is the danger of playing with explosives.
I'm thankful that the bomb connects if it's actually in my line of sight.
Otherwise, I would have been totally screwed.
Oh god, this guy's fast.
You know what?
I need speed.
Give me that.
Oh, that's gonna help me so much.
I was way too slow.
Damn it.
I think we've checked for secrets there.
There we go.
Bloody crown.
A treasure room will appear in the womb and corpse floors.
You know what?
I like it.
I do.
I enjoy that.
I don't know if I enjoy this though.
Kamikaze?
Explode.
Warning.
Damages.
No.
But lunch is more range.
I don't... Guys, I'm gonna skip this one.
Both are bad for me.
What the fuck?
This is the first time that's ever happened.
That's terrible.
Please, rain it down.
That's not gonna matter too much anyway.
Wow.
What the heck was that even?
These fireworks are out of control.
Yep.
Nope.
Tagas.
I don't have a curse right now.
But I think I'll keep it actually.
It makes... Having all this range makes me not want to destroy everything.
It takes too long.
It's too annoying.
Whoa.
Uh, not yet.
In fact, I may not even take that.
Because I kind of want to keep a little extra for like a black heart.
Right?
It's actually bad for me.
Took a little too much damage there.
Moms.
What is it with the range items?
You're kidding me.
These items are bad.
You know what?
Maybe we say fucking and go full range.
I mean at this point, whatever.
Just go full range, man.
Like, I don't care.
What's gonna happen if we pick this up now?
Huh.
Wonder what that's gonna do.
This is very interesting.
Ow!
Well, there it goes.
It's gone now.
Fucking randomized tear effects.
We still haven't found the other secrets.
What is this room?
Oh.
Oh, too bad.
It's death.
Could destroy some of these.
What the?
How did that hit me?
Yeah, I can't even hit these skulls.
It's impossible.
Hey,
now I only have seven coins.
How the?
Oh, man.
Spider.
I didn't mean to do that.
Oh, well.
Dude, school back.
We have to save up for that.
Shit, I'm not gonna be able to destroy these.
Oh, wait.
Maybe I should have checked for... Ah, it's probably okay.
Good.
Wait, how come I have two familiars?
Wait a sec.
Yeah, this is just for the current room.
How come... Why do I have two of these?
Wait, that's confusing.
I don't know.
That's weird.
Huh.
I'm not sure.
I think we just move on, honestly.
I don't know where this secret room is.
I'm not gonna find it.
Yeah.
Maybe here?
Here?
The devil.
Oh, nice.
Okay, there it is.
Lucky.
Another eternal heart.
Oh, a card.
The Empress Dam.
Not what I need.
It's still a pretty good card, though.
This one's better.
Removing the curse is kind of big.
Oh, that's a bomb.
Very delayed one.
Now we can leave.
Let's go.
This is a weird run.
I have no idea how this is gonna go.
We need to find teleport on this floor.
It needs to happen.
Okay.
Speed up.
It's nice.
Wait, we can blow this up.
Oh, yeah, right.
We can get some keys.
Why not?
Okay, dude.
Fucking greedy.
I didn't say you could have all my keys.
The world!
That one is just revealing.
Okay, that's good, though.
This is gonna help.
Okay, golden poop.
Do we have a shop?
There is a shop.
Wait, why is the poop not being... Oh, no, it's gonna take forever.
That's weird.
Nice.
I keep forgetting I have flying.
Whoa.
Oh, I mean, that one I can't avoid.
This flies right back in my face.
It's like pissing against the wind.
So, what?
Okay, what happens if I take this now, though?
Wait, that's bad for me.
I don't want any of that.
Oh,
kind of weird.
I'm in this situation where I don't even want the items, but they're actually worse for me.
Nothing?
Oh, yeah, right.
I can see the whole map.
I don't need to check.
I still have two familiars with me.
Wait, why is that?
Did I get, like, some permanent effect somewhere?
I don't know.
Why are there two of the bomb guys?
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I know what it is.
It's probably just like the character, you know?
It's like a gimmick from the character.
You start with one and then you get two eventually or something.
Because I've had this before.
Yeah!
The fool!
Dude!
That's what we needed.
So nice.
Actually massive.
Um, yeah, I guess we'll use this now then.
Oh, it doesn't do anything.
Because I have full hearts.
Oh, I can't take that heart!
That's so painful!
This is why I didn't want to go full red heart, but yeah.
And dude, okay, we could have had this too.
Actually, that's not gonna help me.
That's the only one that doesn't help me off the teleport once.
No!
Wait, what's happening in here?
Oh, I gotta click the button.
Wait, blood bombs!
Heels for red hearts.
Allows placing bombs from bomb count at zero at the cost of half a heart.
I mean, okay.
I think I like that.
Why not?
The other one is dinner, which is gonna give me nothing of value.
Yeah.
Why not?
Go for it.
Oh, whoa!
Oh!
Key!
Doubles the amount of keys.
Definitely want that.
I don't need the other one.
Wait, uh, go!
Okay, what's this?
Another key.
Oh!
Oh, I could have used the rune now!
Note to self, never use the rune.
Unless you need it.
Damn, that's crazy.
Eh, hurts.
Mom!
Doubles the cake.
The amount of bombs we're gonna be throwing here is crazy.
Damn!
We're taking, uh, let's take the Polaroid this time.
Wait, wait, wait.
The fuck, why is that there?
Anyway, do that.
Okay, uh, let's go.
I think I'm ready.
I can't see the rest of the map anyway, so fuck it.
Eh, there is one thing I want to do.
But I don't know where the shop is from here.
Oh, you know what?
I could take this and heal.
Yeah, why not?
I have so much range anyway, who cares?
Let's go.
Let's just go.
At this point, we're going full range.
We're gonna, the goal is to shoot all the way to Africa.
Get in there!
Getting rich here.
Well, I'm destroying this, it's not gonna matter.
But looking for secrets may be a good idea.
Okay.
Yeah, these bombs are buck wild.
What happened there?
Boiled baby?
Sure.
I actually didn't notice what the red, what the right one was.
I think it was a question mark.
Also, what does this do?
Launch a scattered burst of shots, okay.
Oh, it's doing it automatically, on its own, I see.
The star, ooh!
Oh.
Right.
Ooh, this is gonna be a little...
Kinda want to blow this up.
I feel better now.
Dude, this is what Ipikake is made for.
Or I could have stepped on the button.
How about that?
Oh, man.
It feels wrong to leave that behind, doesn't it?
Oh, God, how are you not dead?
Die!
Wait, why are they not dying?
Hello?
Wait, I gotta click the buttons, maybe.
I don't understand what's happening!
Why are they not dying?
What am I missing?
The run is over!
We're dead!
I don't know what's happening.
It's over.
Why are they not dying?
I have no fucking idea what's going on in this game.
That is so fucked up.
What's that?
Plus one health.
Oh, wait, wait, this one is...
Jumper cables.
Uh, ooh, I mean...
In conjunction with the other battery thing I have?
Could be kinda good.
Also, why is this key like that?
Oh, it just has a different color, I guess.
Now, I wonder, this is just gonna heal one red heart.
That's not good enough.
I was hoping for a full health.
I don't know what happened in that last room.
Like, it's... so weird.
I'm gonna buy this just to get Yes Mother.
Take that back.
Then I'm gonna take these.
Yeah, I mean, I have no fucking idea.
Now I'm super scared of finding a room like that again.
That was weird.
Could be a secret here.
Oh my god, he's so fast.
Nah, I'm actually close to dying here.
Heal me up.
Okay, that's kinda cool actually.
Wait, that means I can duplicate twice?
Wait, I'm not gonna do it again.
What the hell?
Healing, good.
Keep healing me.
So much money though.
Okay, the boss is here.
I'm gonna go for it.
There's really nothing else on this floor.
Actually, there is a bunch of healing.
I spotted it.
There's also a... no, never mind.
We go for the healing.
What's that?
Oh man, that's so sad.
I can't take any of these, huh?
What a tragedy that is.
Oh yeah, this... oh yeah.
Oh yeah, that's nice.
That was very needed.
There's actually another one I can grab.
Dude, this music is kinda nice too.
I didn't really pay attention to it that much, because I was focused on not dying all the other times I was here.
It's good.
I'm gonna take this.
Just for fun.
I like holding onto it, okay?
Dude, I wonder if this means I can duplicate my guys, and then duplicate again, and double it twice, you know?
So I end up with, I don't know, what would that be?
So four... eight?
Guys shooting bombs?
That sounds crazy, right?
Kinda want to save that for the final, final, final boss.
If that actually works that way.
I spent it.
It's gone.
Just get over it.
What do you mean?
How can you have spent our savings?
Oh, AWAS!
Look for decoration.
Not in here.
Treasure?
Oh, right.
I still don't see a decoration!
Yeah, this range is... I can't even see my shots.
This is ridiculous.
The magician... Oh, homing shots!
Dude, I'm gonna save that for the final, final, final, final, final boss.
If that actually works with my bombs, I can just sit there and plink away.
Plink, plink, plink, plink, plink, plink, and they're gonna find their target.
We gotta AWAS first, and then we gotta grab that.
Oh, I almost went into that!
Jesus Christ.
Is this AWAS?
It is AWAS.
Yeah!
What is that?
Yeah, okay, that's fine.
Huh?
Why can't I take it?
Oh, okay.
I thought I had too many familiars or something?
I thought I hit a cap!
So confused.
Okay, give me that.
We're gonna save this magician.
I forgot to grab the heart before I left.
It's okay, though.
Wait, what?
I don't think I'm gonna go in there.
We need to go up.
But why is that there?
I wonder.
I'm too scared.
Dude, I keep hitting myself.
Not looking good.
Nah, bro.
We are actually cooked.
We are so cooked.
How am I gonna get my HP back is the question, though.
I can't even get these blue hearts.
Even if they were to spawn.
I gotta keep going up here.
This is so bad, guys.
I'm fucked.
More range?
Come on.
It's gonna take me to three out of three on yes, mother.
Maybe that's worth it.
I don't know.
We're gonna wait.
Does the other one heal me fully?
No, that's one lock.
Take it.
Oh, right.
It makes a knife.
Useless.
Shit.
Please die.
What?
Wait, are we not done in here?
Oh, I see him.
Oh.
I didn't even see it.
Oh, okay.
So weird.
We're just gonna go up.
At this point, I mean, I'm fucked.
I'm fucked.
It's looking bad, guys.
It's really not looking good.
I'm in deep shit here.
I'm gonna kill myself with these bombs.
It's...
What?
Is even happening.
It's Ogre.
Little Spure has appeared.
At least we got an unlock.
Man, this run went from...
kind of amazing to... what the fuck is going on to...
Ah, we're cooked.
That's the progression.
Okay.
Let's do...
Let's do Judas.
Sometimes when you're at your lowest, you gotta go lower to get into a positive.
I'm feeling it, man.
I'm feeling this guy right now.
Really focus.
That's crazy.
That's exactly what Judas needs!
We are cooking!
Of course, we don't want to go too crazy with the hearts.
We've just been through a cautionary tale.
I don't like that very much.
I'm gonna re-roll when I can.
Which means saving money.
There's nothing I want in here anyway.
This is a weird floor.
A key is nice.
Another key, wow.
Wait, let me think.
I need bombs.
Okay!
Not bad either.
Kind of a crazy start.
Destroy him here.
Yeah!
That was the plan, I swear to God.
I planned that.
It was not accidental.
You may think I'm lying, I'm not.
Stepping time!
Maybe.
This is my favorite part of the script right here.
I'm never a big fan of the starch, but it needs to be done, you know?
This is the good part.
This is where it gets good.
Come here.
Still no bombs though, that's a little frightening.
Because I really, really, really need that.
I'm not gonna get it, am I?
Frick.
That's crazy.
Wow.
Oh wait, I should use this.
Bro, it's not joking.
Oh my goodness, cube of meat.
I don't like that very much.
We're gonna go heal.
I'm not here.
Ah, down here.
We have plenty of healing here.
Wish I could step somewhere though.
Isn't that kind of sad?
Like, not even a curse room?
Man.
The one time I get all the hearts, you know?
Now we gotta try and find a buffer.
Chances are we're not gonna keep...
We're holding on to...
Chances are we're not gonna hold on to the red hearts.
But we reach the boss.
What a shot!
And there's my bomb.
Little too late, mister.
Oh, sick.
Now we know we can head inside the curse room and not actually lose Angel Chance.
But I'm not gonna do it until we have some healing.
Oh god.
Wow.
That's a good one.
I had to read that twice.
That's very nice.
We got the buffer.
I also need keys now.
That's gonna be an AWAS.
It's like us.
Okay, whatever.
That's the one that removes the curse, right?
Dude, this is going pretty well.
And here's the boss.
We got three buffers.
I mean, come on.
This is going great.
Judas is actually delivering.
Can you believe it?
Focus now.
Lock in.
Oi!
That's kinda close.
We're going for Angels.
Just because it's Judas and we're low on everything.
Got one bomb.
Wish I had more.
I got 15 coins, which means I really want a key now.
To get into the shop room.
Uh...
I was about to say, do I keep the other one, though?
I'm not sure.
Let me think.
The damage up is nice, right?
But being able to fly and stuff is also pretty damn good.
I think it may be better to have this.
Uh...
Damn!
Alright!
So wait, I wonder...
Uh...
No, nevermind.
Yeah.
I'm good with that.
We're gonna leave treasure shop room behind, which sucks, but you know.
Guess what it is.
Let me just double check now.
So, checklist.
Before we enter, I go down.
Uh...
Am I misremembering something?
Let me see.
Shop room...
We can't do that.
Treasure room, we got everything.
That room, we got everything.
I think we're good.
Let's go.
This is what I need to do every time I step onto a new floor, you know?
I need to do the checklist.
Catacombs.
We got a huge buffer, so we're definitely gonna be ready for the angel.
We gotta calm down here.
I lost way too much HP in here.
That should not have happened.
Oh.
Stay back!
No!
I still have a freaking key!
Insane.
Boy.
Key acquired.
Little chat.
That's actually not bad.
But that means we gotta find some more red hearts.
Man, man, man, man.
God!
Good thing I have this buffer, huh?
Otherwise, everything would have went to shit.
It still kinda is, but you know.
Doesn't feel like I have that much damage, even though I do.
Let's go!
Dark Wand.
Oh no.
I hate when you do that.
What do you do now?
Want to do a laser or something?
No, charging.
Focus.
Nice, he went into the fires.
Oh.
Oh God.
Get him.
Ooh, nice.
And breakfast as well, that's so huge on this character.
Ooh, we gotta get three out of three on seraphim.
I forgot what that does.
Wait, did I write it down?
Let me see.
Maybe I did write that down.
Let's see here.
No.
I have not written that down.
And this one is...
We don't know what that is, but that's probably a shitty familiar.
Look at it.
That's a familiar.
I want this.
A sworn friend.
Oh, it's flight!
Okay, write it down.
Write it down.
I'm just gonna write it here.
Seraphim, three out of three is flight.
Nice.
And something else on this?
Slow homing tears, right?
Okay.
We could blow this guy up.
I'm not gonna do it.
I'm not interested in that.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, man.
Flying is good!
Now we need spectral tears.
And then we're chilling.
And more bombs.
Yeah, now it feels like I'm doing way more damage.
Maybe it's just seraphim helping.
Something feels different.
Compass.
Or I re-roll!
Ooh, that's tempting.
I don't really care about this one too much.
Um, that guy was that one.
I don't like this either.
Shit.
Maybe I can re-roll again.
We're not done on this floor.
I'll be back.
I could also blow up the machine to re-roll.
Let's not forget that.
I just wanna double-check everything first.
Wait, hagalas!
Uh, there was one room in here that I forgot where it was, but where we could possibly use this.
I need to think on that.
Because I remember at one point thinking, man, I wish my current one was a hagalas.
Oh, that opened.
Let's do it then.
That's for you!
That was sick.
Clean.
Ooh!
Saving that one.
We're not gonna forget it!
We are not gonna forget that!
Lock it in your mind.
Do not move on without it!
Hear me?
Do not move on without it.
Okay.
Two bombs, three keys.
And we got this...
You know what?
Do it here.
Give me the mushrooms.
Okay, why not?
I'll take that.
Uh, back to the shop, I guess.
We got 18 coins.
We can possibly re-roll.
And if not, we're gonna bomb re-roll.
Oh, I should have used hagalas here!
That's what I was thinking of!
This was the room.
This was the room where I had to thought, fuck me.
Why didn't I trust myself?
What's this?
It's not good!
Actually...
Variable charge based on the last pill copied.
No, I need Bible.
I like my Bible.
No, actually, I don't need Bible, because I can fly!
Bible is shit now!
But I don't want that.
Mmm, actually...
The fool!
I need that one.
Guess I'm using this.
Very nice.
Now we have insurance.
For the future.
We're leaving.
I think, uh, it's going pretty well here.
Oh my god, my god, my god, my god, my god!
I almost forgot!
Whoo!
I almost forgot.
Ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
That was a close one.
I almost forgot that one.
Yoink!
Dude, I was so ready to leave.
Man.
Dude, I feel like watching Gone in 60 Seconds.
You know the one with the one true god?
I haven't watched that in a while.
Let's go.
Come on, Judas!
Flooded calves.
That feeling when your calves are flooded.
I hate that feeling.
Uh, hairpin?
Fully charges Isaac's active item when entering a new button.
That is a pretty good amount of charge we're going to get, though.
I actually like that.
Call me crazy.
But then again, then again, then again.
We are kind of going to need the fool.
But I guess it's still good to generate, you know, temporary cards.
I need to think on it.
Two keys, I'm going to use them.
Whoa, we got money.
Whoa, die shards.
Let's not forget.
This one is not a normal one.
This one re-rolls all items and pickups.
Everything.
Shit!
Well, may as well have forgotten the... oh, well.
Wait, why didn't I do that in here?
I'll be back for the fool.
I'll come back.
We're going to use this die shard somewhere.
Somewhere smart.
I'm using too much HP.
Blow him!
I need pills!
Wait, what is this?
I guess I can do this.
Dude,
I almost didn't think.
I'm glad this doesn't actually affect angels.
I just realized.
As soon as I did, I was like, uh-oh.
Sure.
Okay.
Probably should have spawned that outside that room.
We're not perfect.
What?
Excuse me.
Cart.
Uh...
Uh, I'll have a jump.
Come on.
We're going east.
Shit!
Almost got hit.
I clutched it.
You know why they... if they ever were to make a car, you know, in my image, they wouldn't need a clutch in there, because I'm the clutch.
How dare you.
Fucking inanimate objects.
Strike again.
Okay, turn off.
Good.
Two of spades is bombs.
No, it's keys.
Actually, I like it.
So, the bosses here, we're going to use the D6 in there.
Right, he does that.
I like the stones!
Dude,
I ran into it.
Okay, what do we got?
Uh, see, I actually kind of hate this one, so I am going to re-roll that.
Oh!
Even worse.
A chance to spawn a key each time I pick up a coin.
Uh, we're not taking demons, as per the rule of the day.
The rule is no demon.
It is not allowed.
How am I so bad at this game?
It's astounding.
That's what the cower would sound like.
Wish I had a cower.
I'm not allowed to have a cower.
I'm going to go south.
Sorry,
I just thought of a joke.
I see this.
Made me laugh.
Kill it!
Okay, so far so good.
Dude, I have good attack speed.
Hey!
Oh my god!
Another fool!
Cool.
Let's have a duel.
With a moo!
What is that one, Pisces?
More tears?
Bigger?
Yo!
That's a massive item for me.
That's a really nice item.
This is a horrible room.
I cry every time.
I actually dodged that like a boss.
Kind of want to go back to those beggars and give them HP.
Is that weird?
We did the boss already.
So whatever, right?
Yeah, let's do it.
I need some kind of return on all that investment.
Right now it's just money out the window.
Or HP.
Sucking cost fallacy!
No!
That's all you got?
Okay, fuck you.
No!
Wait, we gained a...
Oh, wait a minute.
We gained a bunch of Angel for that.
That's kind of interesting.
See, I could have used the fool there and then grabbed the other fool, but I was a little afraid that I was miscalculating things.
I wasn't because it's right here.
But you know, blade safe and all that.
Habada habada, right?
Four bombs, we could look for a secret.
I think there's a secret right here.
Source, trust me bro.
Okay, don't trust me.
Damn, it was right in the center of everything though.
I feel like that's the rule.
I would say 60% of the time it works every time.
But it's not every time.
That's like the catch, you know?
There's another red heart down here I'm going to grab and then we're going to leave.
There we go.
I'm out of here.
Solid.
We got the fool.
Mom is calling.
We got a Duertos.
Ugh.
What's the thought of that?
Get in there.
Do I want this?
No, no, no.
Keep going.
Alright, so next one is Mom.
Turn around.
Hands up.
Hands behind your back.
Good enough.
These inanimate objects are going to ruin my day.
Just going to hide back here.
Solid strategy.
That was a hard one there.
The Empress is...
Speed?
Okay.
Nah, we don't need that.
Gimme.
I have two hats on.
That's against the law.
Whoa!
What was that?
Did you see the way he just abandoned his path and went on his own...
path?
Weird.
Oh, I missed you.
It's going to be messed up.
Oh, even more money.
47 coins.
And there's a shop.
Please don't let it be a shit shop.
Let it be a good one.
Come on, please.
Yes!
Uh, let me see.
Pokego...
I guess we'll take it, right?
There's no reason not to buy it.
Give me that one.
And what's this?
Yay!
Nice.
I'm going to get a key as well.
We're buying everything.
And we're going to donate.
I took money out of the box today.
We're going to give it back.
There's probably a crazy unlock behind giving the donation box more money, right?
Like, we're talking maybe a thousand.
I feel like I should start focusing on that.
But it's also so difficult because I need the money a lot of the time.
Okay, boss is here.
Two of clubs is bombs.
Yes.
Give me more.
Uh, this should...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is not, uh...
God, I forgot.
I don't remember if this is Mom.
I think it's the next one that's Mom.
I'm going to keep the fool on me just in case, though.
But let's go over here.
Okay, what are you doing in here?
That's a lot of money.
Rich get richer.
What's that?
No, I don't need that.
Child leash is not for me.
Lord!
That is actually a question, isn't it?
Because that's a lot of less speed, but I'm taking it.
It's two hearts, man.
I gotta do it.
Now we're a little bit fat.
It's okay.
We're gonna work it off.
Do some calisthenics and some...
Why are people getting small now?
I don't know.
Oh, it's probably the mushroom having a random effect on them.
Yeah, that's it.
Now I'm really slow.
But I feel like there's a lot of speed in the game.
I should be able to find some more.
I'm going in here.
Nice!
That's really nice.
Oh my goodness!
What the heck, man?
What a great room.
I almost used the fool instinctively.
Two of hearts.
Uh, no.
It's time to leave.
We have done everything we can.
Maybe go back to the shop and check it out now that we have 18 coins.
It would be nice.
But I think I bought everything.
Donate more!
It broke!
Good.
Now we can move on.
Feeling good about ourselves.
This guy's gonna get owned.
He's not even doing anything.
Almost got hit.
I'm gonna do Hitless.
Yeah!
Beautiful.
More tears!
We got the angel!
Oh, it's looking up.
It's looking up.
This is a good one.
When all red hearts are full, tears become diamonds and gold.
Nice!
Taking damage removes the effect for the room.
And this one was...
Replaces tears with large piercing bursts of holy energy.
The bursts deal reduced damage but can damage enemies multiple times as they pass through.
That's also good!
Oh my god!
And Monstrance!
And it's a large golden aura that deals damage to enemies within it.
Enemies take more damage from the aura the closer they are.
This one is more guaranteed, like long-term.
If I lose all my blue hearts, then this one is gonna be bad.
Because I'm not gonna be able to sustain full red hearts.
I think I'm gonna go for this one.
Play it safe.
And yeah.
Thank you very much, sir.
I appreciate it.
And I'll see you later.
Imagine if I could take all three.
Damn!
That would be crazy.
Okay, so this is the floor with Mom.
Oh my god!
That's awesome!
Dude, I shoot so fast!
Bombs get bigger, yeah.
That's fine.
Let's try it in here.
That's awesome.
Very nice.
Dude, there's spectral too?
Did it say that?
Piercing bursts of holy energy.
It says piercing, not spectral though.
So that's news to me.
Well, that's cool.
I like it.
Dude, it looks crazier than it is, I think.
Like, the damage is not that great.
Maybe the diamonds would have been better.
I was just taken with the whole effect, you know, like, like, not that much damage.
I mean, it's not bad.
But it's...
Yeah, I mean, it's fine.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
It's pretty good.
I like it.
I mean, let's not look a gift horse in the mouth, okay?
You look fortunate.
Uh, no.
Not right now.
I mean, this just looks insane.
Wow.
Uh, what's going on here?
It's going pretty well.
Who would have thunk?
Judas!
Oh, yeah.
The stars!
Uh, let's try it.
Aw, too bad.
I was hoping for a planetarium.
One thing I need though is more speed.
I'm a little too slow right now.
If I can get that, then we're cooking.
Right now, we're just chopping the veggies, you know?
The oil is in the pan, but it's not really sizzling.
We gotta get it to the sizzle states.
Okay, get up here.
Mom!
What's going on, Mom?
There's more, I know there's more, there's not more, okay.
Uh, do we go for it yet?
We haven't found the shop though.
We gotta find the shop first.
What?
Bullshit.
Oh, it's so nice against these guys.
Shop located.
Yo, that laser's gonna be banging.
That's a banging laser now.
I'm gonna buy this too.
The devil, uh, no.
I can't don it anymore.
Yeah, we're done.
Time to leave.
Dude, this laser dude is gonna be hurting, okay.
He's gonna hurt a lot.
Wow, that was crazy.
Insane damage.
We're gonna take more damage.
We're gonna go in here.
Oh, this one is not that great.
It's okay.
Definitely could have gotten something better there.
But, uh, out we go.
I almost jumped down the hole.
Glad I didn't.
Here we go!
Let's do this!
Masulium.
These tear effects look insane.
Dude, it's almost like the game is telling me I should be giving this guy hearts, with all the hearts around.
Haha.
Okay, come on.
Come on.
Give me something.
Whoo!
Chance to fire... Whoa!
That's gonna go hard.
Whoa!
Yeah, yeah, I like that.
I like it.
That's cool.
I'm not hitting anything, because I'm a dumbass and I can't aim.
Wait, why am I not... Oh, maybe I don't have spectral cheers.
But why does it visually look like they go through things then?
That's a bit confusing.
Is that a pajamas?
What does that do?
Is this all red hearts?
Oh, okay.
It is cozy.
You're buffered right now.
Cozy feeling.
I mean, these guys are just useless, aren't they?
Look at that!
Ancient recall?
Three random cards.
Yeah.
Hearts?
Uh, no.
Nice.
That's a good one.
We're gonna save it.
What's that?
Shit.
Well, that's not good.
That's really bad, actually.
I don't know where I got extra speed from.
You know what?
We're gonna go inside the curse room.
I have good feelings about it.
Nevermind.
Fine.
Wasn't there a blue heart somewhere?
Nah.
Hierophant?
And this one is the Empress.
Don't really need that.
Take one of these.
120 volt?
Electrify is ice sick.
I'm automatically sapping enemies in close range.
The saps can chain up to four.
That's not super good for me.
I'm gonna gamble.
The sad onion tears up.
Nice.
Okay.
I mean, that's gonna be more DPS.
I like that.
Health down.
No, thanks.
You know what?
It could actually be in common handy.
If I had too many, you know?
But I don't.
What if I had?
Only five coins.
Please don't be a good item in here.
Not really that exciting.
Give me this one back.
Maybe if I find some coins, I'll consider it.
Yeah, so I definitely don't have spectral tears, even though it looks like it.
It's a bit odd.
Here we go.
I'm gonna go for it.
Wish me luck.
Here we go.
I spent it.
It's gone.
Just get over it.
If you mean it's gone.
It's gone.
How would you have spent our savings?
Uh, right.
I'm surprised every time that there's nothing in there.
An attack fly appears?
What?
What even is this right here?
Who was that?
That's Stephen's uncle?
Yeah, go!
Oh, we could... Wait, how does that work?
No, we're gonna keep this.
The sun!
That's a good one!
Definitely saving that.
Wait, what else does it do?
Reveals?
The thing is though, it doesn't give me extra damage.
It does heal me though.
So I think for that reason, it's worth it to keep.
Just for the healing.
Oh, right, so... Mom was called Maggie.
Some reason I thought my sister was Maggie.
Go!
What?
Wait, opens the door to a red room and use next to a valid wall?
Huh?
Crack key?
Wait, do we have to look for that again?
Dude, I'm gonna be scanning the shit out of these walls.
What do you mean?
Why is that just there?
I don't understand what's happening.
I see nothing.
Wait, I see something.
No, fuck!
Wrong button.
Huh?
Come here.
Weird.
I feel like there should be more in there, but okay.
Maybe that's just me.
I mean, I appreciate the... Wait, what's this?
The lovers.
No.
I'm gonna get my sun back.
I'm not gonna leave my sun behind.
I do need to find more blue hearts though.
Or black hearts.
Key?
Dude, I hate when he makes the sound when he shoots.
Makes me think there's an enemy.
Okay.
You need to repent.
You need to confess your sins and become saved.
Let his light inside you cleanse your soul.
You are insane.
You are taking this too far.
Can't you hear how you sound?
Fuck!
What?
Oh, man.
I fucked it up.
I did.
I may as well do it.
I have so many bombs, right?
Oh, nice.
Yeah, I should have done that.
That was bad.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Why did I just run into that?
I'm not nearly fast enough for that maneuver.
Here.
This guy has a lot of HP.
What's happening?
Why is he still tanking?
What?
No way.
Hey!
50 bombs now.
It's actually not bad.
We're losing HP.
Stars?
Oh.
I wouldn't mind finding the Hierophant.
That would be good.
That would be really nice.
No?
Unfortunate.
Scary.
So many red hearts, man.
Why are there so many?
Okay.
I mean, my damage is good.
Another one?
Huh.
I'm gonna blow this up.
Just for fun.
Wasn't that fun?
Empty.
I don't even think I need this money anymore.
It don't even matter.
Pills, please be... well, I don't know what I want, actually.
I guess maybe one of these flies that orbit me would be nice.
The stars again?
Man, my damage is good.
Okay, fine.
Basement one.
We're almost there.
Oh, right!
Dude, I forgot about this room!
We came back for it!
No way!
It's okay.
Ooh.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on now.
This may actually be bad for me.
I'm gonna reroll that one.
I'm not gonna ruin this right now.
I'm too scared.
Ha!
I don't think that's good.
Actually, I have six tiers now.
That would be three-point-something tiers.
We roll.
I don't believe in it.
Monster was long.
Tears become a charge attack.
Isaac spits a mouthful of sh- Oh, that's also risky as fuck, dude!
I can't do it.
Oh, no!
You know what?
I'm fine.
I'm fine, because probably if I had taken one of these others, I probably would have ruined the build.
So this is for the best.
The game was telling me, don't do it!
Just stick with what you have, you know?
We have a way to spend our money now.
Dessert!
Hey, not bad!
Awesome!
Actually, do this.
What is this?
Dude, they spawn a lot of crap.
Dude, it is so good at clearing little guys.
It's weird that they go through these things, but they don't actually go through.
The animation is lying to me.
The hangman?
Dude,
I need to find a little bit more damage.
Imagine finding, like, just a bit more damage.
It would amplify this so much.
In fact, I think if I had stuck with the card that gave me plus two damage, it may have been better than the sun.
Plus two damage is actually crazy right now.
Here we go!
We're home!
A lot of useless money.
Thanks.
Okay.
Dude, I kind of wonder, what if I hadn't used that key?
Like, could I have used it here?
Like last time?
Maybe you have a choice.
I'm going
to try and blow up this TV every time.
One of these times is going to work.
Trust.
Red key!
Opens nearby doors to mysterious hidden rooms while the outlines of these hidden doors can be seen on certain walls?
Yes?
Let me scan the walls.
Wait, this is the same one as last time.
Let's keep looking around.
I don't want to do the same thing.
Okay, I don't see any.
All right, guess I'll have to use it there.
Or not?
Maybe I save it for later.
Ah, use it.
Oh,
shit!
Okay!
I get it now!
You got to do this exact thing on every character to unlock their, I don't even know, like, dark side or whatever.
Give me that back.
No, actually, keep this.
Just in case, right?
We don't know what's going to happen.
Wait, why is nothing happening here?
All right, I got to go to bed.
Here we go!
This is still going to be hard, man.
I may have to take this just because...
Who knows what it'll get me?
Maybe I spawn a sun that is so clutch, right?
I got to, I got to... I'm taking it.
I'll come back for the, no, I can't come back for that.
I guess it doesn't matter.
Come on!
I need to, I need to focus now.
I can easily fuck this up.
Dogma!
No, how did I get hit?
No problem.
Okay, here we go, here we go.
I'm locked in, man.
Get rekt, son!
Get rekt!
Here we go, here we go, here we go.
I'm going to drop bombs on his face.
My bombs do more damage, right?
I have good bombs.
Oh, maybe it's not worth it right now, actually.
He's too mobile.
Yeah, here comes the next one.
No wait, he's not done.
He's not done.
This dude has no chill.
I missed him.
What's happening now?
I don't remember.
Oh, he's spawning little guys, that's fine.
I'm an expert at clearing little guys with this build.
No problem.
Cart, another sun?
Wow!
Oh, but wait, my other sun is in the lava.
It actually spawned another sun.
Can you believe that?
I feel like that's kind of crazy.
How?
Did you see that strategic bomb placement?
It was beautiful.
Come on, then.
This guy I don't quite remember.
Oh, right, he does that stuff.
Oh, god.
That was bad.
What the hell is this?
I haven't seen this before.
That's new.
Here we go!
It's a beast!
He be coming.
I'm gonna lock in, lock in, lock in, lock in.
Dude, my tears are destroying the spikes!
That's freaking awesome!
Uh oh.
How the fuck do you dodge this?
Sun!
Use it!
Use the fucking sun!
You motherfucker!
Whoa!
You bastard!
How am I supposed to dodge that shit?
What does the Empress do?
More damage!
Yes!
Damage me!
I mean, damage him!
Come on.
We gotta clutch this.
Ha ha!
That's how we do it, baby!
Oh no, I can't watch that again, man.
It's gonna fuck me up.
I don't wanna know about it.
It's too sad.
Okay, win streak of one.
We're back.
Where?
Jutas!
He's a shadow eater!
What does that mean?
I don't know what my HP is.
I have dark arts.
Isaac gains a shadow form for one second.
That grants invincibility.
Speed up.
And he can walk through enemies to mark them.
When the shadow form ends, deals damage to all marked enemies.
If multiple enemies are marked, each one takes more damage than the previous one.
And, each marked enemy and projectile grant a stacking plus one damage up that depletes rabbit.
Why is it in the bottom right, though?
I'm not in the... Huh?
I'm scared.
Oh, I'm like an assassin!
Dude, that is awesome.
Jutas, I love you.
Maybe.
Oh no, don't...
Is that common cold?
Wait, I wonder.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, I can't get in there.
That's too bad.
I want to know how much HP I have, though.
Like, what's up with that?
I like that.
I gotta get that.
Gotta get some money here.
Oh my god!
Oh, and then I get damage up!
Oh, sick!
I see how it works!
Oh my god.
Yes!
Wait, I can't take that?
That means I have no red hearts.
Damn, okay.
So I guess I only have black hearts, or what?
Oh god.
I think I was a little too slow on that, I'm not sure.
What's that?
Pop!
Eyeball Tears.
It places tears with eyeball shots that can bounce off of each other.
Eyeball shots are not limited by range, and last until they run out of momentum or until they hit an enemy.
Or what?
I need to see that.
Huh.
I guess that's cool.
I'm not sure what to think about that.
Dude!
This is awesome!
That is incredible.
I missed one.
No!
I thought it was ready, it wasn't.
I was bamboozled.
Hahaha!
Dude, okay, I mean, this is awesome.
Wow.
I'm just gonna keep doing that.
Watch this.
Hahaha!
Dude, that's crazy.
HP up is good, I guess, but I don't know how much HP I have, it's kinda weird.
Ah, let's see here.
I think I just, oh wait, if I have HP up now, I can probably grab the green heart.
Let's check it out.
Okay, so we've confirmed that red hearts do not exist on this character.
Maybe because we're black, you know?
We gotta get black hearts only.
It's like, yeah, something like that.
Alright, let's go.
Second floor, now we gotta start, but the good part is, we don't have to worry about buffers.
Because we are the buffer.
Yeah, look, two black hearts.
Okay, let's do this.
I would say the keybind is awkward though for that.
I kinda, I wish it was space instead, maybe I can change that.
Oh, only in the menu, I think.
It's so weird that you can only do it in the menu, what's the point of that?
Like, why not, you know?
We're gonna play this so safe.
I don't like these eyeballs.
That is actually so dope.
Oh, almost got hit by that.
Wait, the last guy got hit as well, even though I didn't run into him.
What's up with that?
Weird.
I could use a bomb there, but I'm not gonna.
Can I just use this?
Oh my god!
I love this character.
These guys would have been so annoying, not on this guy.
Hey!
I mean, come on.
That's dope!
I need shot speed.
Oh no, I can't get in there.
Oh, there's an X though!
Wait, why are we blinking?
Look at that.
If we're standing on the thing, that's weird.
We haven't even found the treasure room though, hold on.
We can't move on, not yet.
Let's go up here.
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
Why are you doing this to me?
Sure.
Yes, we'll do it.
Five coin arenas.
Not a lot.
Wait, if I do this... hold on.
Someone's a random familiar that lasts...
If I take this battery, I can have two?
Or...
Who the fuck is that?
Look at that, baby!
Golden hair?
Weird.
Alright.
I'm gonna go this way.
The virus.
Sure.
War speed is actually good for my Q.
By the way, you may have thought, oh, he got so lucky there that he destroyed...
he marked a rock on accident.
It was planned.
I saw it, okay?
I know, that was pretty cool.
I had to acknowledge it.
I had to acknowledge that.
He hit me.
Oh, you... you motherfucker.
Give me that.
We are not doing demons!
No!
No demons.
Full angel.
Love it!
Kinda wanted to spawn something and then run through it.
Maybe let him spawn a couple.
Didn't even die from that.
Bitch.
Oh, okay, so I can... ah, nice.
Now I can chariot and then I can do the shadow chariot.
Right.
I'm gonna go in here.
That was probably not worth it.
Dude, we're gonna let them spawn a bunch.
Watch this.
I'm gonna threaten them.
Monster manual.
Why is Emmanuel so strong?
Ah, I don't believe in Emmanuel, Emmanuel, Emmanuel.
Ah, I don't believe in Emmanuel.
That's a common folk song in Germany.
I got hit!
Mayday, mayday!
Wow.
Watch this.
No!
We cannot interact with the button in the beepin.
That's too bad.
That was a little bit risky what I did there.
I don't understand these eyes I'm shooting.
I don't like them.
And if I don't understand something, then I don't like it.
I'm kidding.
We lost our hearts.
Absolute tragedy.
Why did one of them die and not the others?
What the hell's up with that?
Maybe the first attack does more damage.
That's kind of weird though.
Here we go.
Pasty lawns.
It's angel time, baby.
Dude, that's so awesome.
I hate this item.
Why do you punish me?
So...
That sucks.
How sad is that?
You know what, check this out.
That's how you do it.
Emmanuel would be proud.
I dedicate this run to Emmanuel.
X-10.
Boring!
I don't want that.
Uh-oh.
I have questions.
I'm not gonna get that, am I?
Fuck.
Wait.
Oh, right.
Yeah, okay.
I thought I just misclicked, but then I didn't misclicked, so it was okay.
It was weird.
Holy shit, that was close.
Getting a little frisky here.
Yeah.
No!
Faster!
Let's go to the shop.
We got some money now.
God, I wish I could fly.
I wish I could touch the sky.
Wait, don't walk through that.
I need buffers.
Yes, okay, that's good, actually.
We are just gonna have to grab it.
I also just noticed that we get half a black heart when we grab this.
If we are at half a black heart already.
That's kind of interesting.
What's up with that?
Here we go.
A lot of angel.
Oh my god, they dodged that.
I'm in shambles.
Didn't even die from it.
I think as long as I'm close to them, then I do the damage.
With the dark arts.
I am an assassin.
PM me.
How on earth did that hit me?
There we go.
That could be good.
Speed, range...
Oh, I thought it was a plus one HP.
Damn.
It's still good, though.
I need flying.
I need set off him.
That is so good.
I hope it scales with my damage.
Does it?
Let me also see here.
Multiple enemies are marked.
Each one takes more damage than the previous one.
Right, okay, so that makes sense.
Right, okay.
Wait, each marked enemy and projectile?
Wait, that's new.
Okay, all right.
Really?
Okay, I need to use that against a lot of projectiles, then.
Shot speed, hey!
That's very nice.
That's what I've been needing with this set up here.
Wait, I wonder if I can...
Nice.
Ah, buffaritos and my pajama dinos.
Wow.
Lovely.
Summon a man.
I have two men.
Bump, bump, bump.
Shot speed is killer!
Oi!
Nice.
Going pretty well.
Oh no, don't go in there, actually.
Damn.
Why am I farting?
You've been marked for death.
Lovely.
I'm not going to enter.
I'm going to enter.
I had to see for myself.
We're going to blow the whole band up here.
No, thanks.
I'm good.
I wonder if we can go into the step room and do a shadow step.
Yo, he took my bad arinos.
Even though I marked him.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Amazing.
Oh, careful.
Fanny pack would go hard.
Or we can re-roll.
Oh wait, fanny pack.
I thought it was backpack, never mind.
Never mind, it doesn't go hard at all.
It goes mild.
Oh, we're going to re-roll for sure.
Let's not accidentally grab that.
A mystery gift?
I definitely want that.
We're going to save it for the angel.
Boom!
This is going to pay off so hard.
Come on, oh come on then.
How did that not slice and dice him?
Did you hear that?
Someone went...
off to the side.
I'm not crazy, right?
I've heard that before in this game.
And I don't know what it is.
It happens randomly.
Okay, here we go.
It's Gordy.
This is the one where he peeks his head out and he's going to do things to me.
Like that.
I'm stuck!
Oh, that was kind of...
You can't go in there, you get stuck on that.
Scary.
I'll take that.
What?
Wait, wait, wait, that's probably really good.
Let's see.
Less tears.
A lot of damage!
Less shot speed plus one health.
Heels all red hearts, homing tears.
Whoa!
That's fucking awesome!
Breath of life.
Holding use depletes the charge bar.
Isaac becomes invincible when the charge bar is empty.
Touching enemies while invincible summons light beams.
Touching an enemy at the same time the charge bar is empty fires a four-way beam.
What?
Repeat that.
Touching an enemy at the same time the charge bar is empty fires a four-way beam.
I get it now.
Holding use after the charge bar is empty causes continual damage to Isaac.
That's scary.
I don't like that part.
This is going to fuck me, isn't it?
I don't know about that, I don't know about that, I don't know about that.
Maybe I go back and grab the other one I have.
I don't like this too much.
Well, I guess we can try it.
Let's just try it.
Fuck it.
We try it, we try it.
Don't be scared.
It's okay.
Just acclimate.
Acclimate.
Oh god.
Wait, it's really fast.
Wait, I need to read that again.
Invincible.
Light beams.
Okay, okay, okay.
Dude, I am like the shadow charger and the light charger.
I strike from the shadows and the light.
I'm not to be trifled with.
Watch this.
I messed it up.
I did, I did.
That's on me.
I'm going to try that again.
After these two die.
Okay.
Dude, I take damage from it though.
What do you mean I'm invisible?
I'm not invisible at all.
Liar.
Hands on fire.
Let me see it again.
Oh yeah, right.
Only while it's down.
But what's the point then?
If I hold it, I'm going to take damage.
Huh?
That's a shit item.
Wait, so you only become invincible when the charge bar is empty?
But when the charge bar is empty, you continually take damage?
What's the point of being invincible then?
I mean, that's a very small window then.
I get it.
That's a very risky item.
Not sure I like that.
Hmm.
What is it with these invincible things?
Uh...
Yeah, I don't need more charitism here.
I have way too much charitism.
Let's try this.
I doubt it's going to work.
Maybe it does work.
Did we trigger that?
No, right?
No.
But maybe with...
Maybe with this.
Okay, it doesn't work.
I've tried all the options.
None of them work.
I'm scared.
Whoo!
Close one.
I'm a Shadow Striker.
Oh, I messed it up.
I don't like this active.
Makes me feel not so good.
Dude, he actually dodged that last moment.
Okay, it's pretty cool.
This is actually insane.
I don't know what's happening, but I really like it.
I need to find a shop.
Right now.
Battery?
Why are we shooting teeth now?
Up!
Man, it's risky as hell.
You really gotta time that.
What is that?
Rock?
Oh, you bastard!
Reading!
Placing a bomb while holding an attack button will instead launch the bomb as a rocket in that direction.
I mean, I may as well do it, right?
We gotta fix this active.
Change it to something else.
I feel like the payoff is not good enough.
But the amount of risk you're taking...
Hold on a minute.
4.5 volts.
No.
Dude, I'm gonna...
We're gonna go all in on the donation now.
Store upgrade what?
I can't wait to see what that means.
Whoa.
More items, maybe.
Why do I keep trying it?
I guess you gotta learn somehow, right?
He got hit by the thingy.
Fated Polaroid.
Wait a minute, I'm the ultimate assassin now.
I'm just confused.
Can't be used to open a strange door!
No shit.
Wait, I wonder what happens if I go in with this guy.
This is like the new version of Judas.
And I enter the home, and I try to look for the red outline.
Are we gonna get a third variation?
Look how slow my shots are without this, though.
Like, it's practically useless.
I would rather just find a teleporter, then.
What was the empress?
Oh my god.
Dude, the damage stays between rooms.
So the faster you go with this guy, the better.
This is the speedrun character.
Nice!
Oh, we got the best hearts, too!
Yo!
Insanity!
Look at him hiding back there!
Oh, I mis-timed it!
I mis-clicked it.
I missed everything there.
Blood clot, okay, sure.
Ooh, wait!
I wonder, am I permanently crowned, then?
Because I don't have any red hearts, right?
I can't tell.
Oh no, oh no, I may not be.
But if I have this, if I get the Eternal Heart!
If I get the Eternal Heart, then it's all good.
Oh wait, the crown is on my head now.
Oh, but that's just a visual, okay.
Uh, I don't... take it.
We are done on this floor anyway.
Yeah, we're going!
Moving on.
Wait a minute, we have 17 damage?
It must be active.
You can't explain that.
Whoa!
I'm unstoppable, I'm the assassin from the shadows.
I kill.
I'm faster than the eye can see.
Nice, we're gonna get more.
Right there.
The one we need!
Those are my last two keys.
Huh?
Why's there so much?
I can only hold so much.
I'm good.
I'm gonna save my last key.
Not fair.
Look at me go.
Dude, I'm kind of killing it.
This is freaking awesome.
Acid baby.
It drops a pill every seven rooms.
That is amazing.
Assuming a pill triggers acid baby to instantly damage all enemies the current room and poison them.
Cool.
I like.
I can't shadow step on the freaking poops.
Literally unplayable.
That was a coin.
Wait, do I have homing tears or something?
What's happening there?
Wait, I have homing tears.
I don't know why.
Cool.
I got no idea why I have homing tears.
Bring it on, mom.
Okay, I kind of messed that one up.
I did, I did.
Fucking wrecked.
Did you see that execution?
Was that beautiful or what?
Look at his plus seven damage?
What the... seven damage?
That's insanity.
That is so much.
We're not leaving yet though, because I need to go to the shop with all my money.
They'll only have one key.
Just kind of messed up.
This one?
No way.
Give me the money I need.
Okay, fine.
I'll take it.
No, wait, we're not done here.
We're not done here anyway.
Fuck!
Didn't mean to.
That was a mistake.
I donated accidentally.
Why didn't he get hit by lightning?
I would have had enough if I didn't donate that money coin.
Can you believe it?
I better find another coin.
I'm excited.
At least we got another key.
That's something.
Yeah, there it is.
Good shit.
I forgot what I needed the money for.
There was something I wanted to buy.
What was it?
I don't remember.
Guess I'll find out.
Wait, there's nothing I... Wait, why did I want 15 coins again?
There's nothing I want in here.
Actually, wait, the battery allows active items to store... Huh?
Maybe that will do something crazy for me?
So how's that gonna work?
Let me see.
I thought maybe I could hold it for longer, but that's how that works.
It's like a... It's a lie.
Oh man, imagine if I could hold it for an entire battery worth.
That's too bad.
Oh well.
I had to try it.
Okay, let's leave.
We're done.
Actually, we're not done.
We're almost done.
I just want to grab this.
Nah, that's not gonna be worth it.
Terrible idea.
I'm gonna go south, left, and up.
I fucked up.
Guess we're going down.
Yep, that had to happen at some point.
Oh, okay then.
Shit balls.
I can't believe it, man.
That's actually hilarious.
I'm so sorry.
Oh no.
What have I done?
Dude, I have a lot of damage.
I one shot that hand.
No, mom.
Really, you gotta do me like that?
Oh, I honestly, I stopped questioning why things happen.
They just do, okay?
The door opens for mysterious reasons.
Nobody knows why, it just happens.
Appell for me.
That hurt my soul.
Oh my god, really?
We may be throwing the run right now.
This may be the end.
I can feel it.
I can feel a throw coming.
Gotta get to that secret room.
I knew what's gonna happen.
I saw it coming.
Why did I do it?
At least we got this for free.
Come on, please be good.
I need blue hearts.
Yes, that's it.
Uh, down here.
Uh, here?
Huh?
Okay, dude.
Whatever you say.
The throw is coming.
Oh, something's wrong.
Something's definitely wrong right now.
I can't see anything because of the text.
Okay, let's go to the boss.
Wow.
Secret room.
Wait, which secret room?
Whoops.
Oh, okay.
Huh.
I guess it always prioritizes that one, or?
Conquest.
Honestly, maybe just attack him because I have such good damage anyway.
There's no reason to start being fancy here, you know?
Uh, ooh, actually, yes.
That's a much better active.
Jesus juice.
Uh, sure.
Why not?
It's not really the best, but whatever.
Oh, really?
What?
Come on.
One at least.
I've been robbed.
That was pure robbery right there.
Oh, well.
Dude, we have four HP.
It's not looking good.
I don't even know how I'm gonna survive this.
I'm so scared of a spiky one.
I'm excited.
No, I don't want that.
Cool.
Blood donation?
Nah, I'm gonna blow that up.
No, I think mine is better.
Yeah, we can get in here.
Wait a sec.
Holy shit!
We can go crazy with the dark arts!
We have two charges on that one too!
Whoa!
Oh, that's amazing.
That's like the ultimate oh shit button now.
What's this?
Oops.
Puberty.
Sure.
Money.
No spike.
Chance will inflict burn.
Increases with luck.
Removes.
No, I think I want to keep my speed.
Otherwise, these would be so slow.
Three bombs walk into a bar.
You can definitely have some bombs.
Actually, no, I don't need money.
And I kind of need the bombs actually for bosses.
Give me HP up.
Thank you.
I'm gonna leave that there.
Let's see how slow they are.
Yeah, look at this.
Look how bad that is without the whip worm.
Gotta whip up some boats.
I have to remember I can fly as well.
I'm not used to that right now.
Experimenting a little bit here with my...
stuff.
Oh, come on.
Open, open.
Good.
That's actually big.
We're getting some good HP here.
This is important.
Lots of battery too, if we need to.
Fish hit.
No.
We play it safe.
Now we hit this way.
Dude, you know what we're gonna do?
We're gonna soak up a million projectiles and then go like and deal so much damage.
Come on, please.
Shit.
Where's my health up?
Pill.
I think the dark arts scales with my damage.
It has to, right?
Those are scary.
Wow.
Did he actually just jump at the right time when I was charging him?
It's kind of crazy.
I don't want to blow him up.
I'm gonna blow only... Oh wait, I can just fly in there.
I'm an idiot.
Give me HP up.
Awesome.
It's about time that we get some good pills.
He jumped over my sneak attack again.
It's impressive.
Here's the boss.
I think we're going for it.
Hippity ho!
The damage is unbelievable.
You've never seen something like this before in your life.
We're going down, baby.
Down.
Further down into hell.
We gotta punish a certain someone.
Whoa.
Come on.
It's a good pill.
Yeah.
Nice.
Not quite HP up though, but you know, I take it.
This guy has HP.
I need... Oh, the fucking spike.
I was fearing that.
Lemon party.
You want to join in?
It's gonna be a lot of fun.
Uh, what's happening here?
Oh.
North.
Oh no, not these guys.
Wait, what?
Uh, I'm gonna view.
Oh, I see him.
I see him.
Jesus Christ, this room is insane.
Yo, what?
Wait, why is that happening?
Hold on.
Why are the lights coming down?
That's not normal.
Oh, no, that is normal.
It's very much normal.
It's in the description of the item.
That's how normal it is.
I'm scared of spiky chests.
Gonna end me.
I want secret rooms.
And I want them now.
The way they all converged.
I'm not gonna open that.
What are you trying to do, huh?
Oh, you bastard.
I'm gonna die.
Oh, God.
I'm surprised I'm still alive.
I am.
Shit.
I forgot he did that.
Where are my hearts at?
Okay, you, you, give me hearts.
Come on, man.
I need it.
You gotta help me out.
Hey, pills are good.
Wait, that's not a good pill.
What the fuck?
Oh, wait, it is actually.
Maybe.
Is everyone else slowed?
And not me?
Is that what's happening?
Ah,
no, not these chests.
They make me sad.
Don't spike me.
Okay.
I'm terrified.
Where are they?
Oh, my goodness.
Here's... Oh, guys.
We're gonna die.
We
may have to go collect a bit more HP first.
I just don't trust, you know?
Not like that.
Don't spike.
Okay.
Where are the blue flames at?
Oh, my God.
There's one more room here.
Don't get hit.
Don't spike me.
Wait, I wonder.
Did not work.
That was the same time.
Okay.
Puberty.
That's one healing.
Yep.
We have reached adult.
Dude, look at this pit in the center.
You can barely see me.
I look terrifying.
Oh, God.
He took my heart.
I God.
Okay.
Wish me luck.
This is it.
I'm going to die.
Wait, I'm actually going to blow this up.
Wait.
What?
Why?
Why did that happen?
Was that an X?
Did I actually destroy a tinted rock without realizing?
Hold on a minute.
I got to go back to that big room with the big pit.
Oh.
Okay.
Hold on a minute.
I'm not done.
We can actually go in here.
No.
Uh, open this.
What?
Wait, creates a ring around Isaac that has a chance to reflect enemy.
I need that.
Enemies inside the ring take Isaac's damage once per second.
Dude, I need this.
I need survival right now.
And we're gonna, we're gonna, we're gonna get this.
Come on.
Blue heart me.
What?
Fuck, that was close.
Wait.
How does that work?
It doesn't work.
Okay.
Rip.
All right.
Cool.
Uh, let's go to the boss.
Wait, why am I getting mana like that?
Actually, there's still some rocks here.
Oh, wait.
I should have probably saved these for the boss.
All right.
It's fine.
It's okay.
Satan?
Now.
Oh,
you dead son.
No, I'm also dead.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
Yeah.
Here, here come the feet.
The feet are coming.
What a sad way to end.
Still, though, it was a cool, it was a cool one.
It was a good run.
Can't be mad about it.
Right?
Not bad.
What a, yes, what a cool character, huh?
It's not my favorite, though.
I will say the, uh, the new Essaysl is still the best.
Closely followed by normal Essaysl.
Also called Nessaysl.
Cobra Judas.
Dude, he was such an assassin.
I feel like I got all the items that allowed me to turn into, like, a different dimension and rush through enemies.
Nessaysl.
Oh, that was, I need to calm down a bit after that.
I was so...
Dude, I had him, man.
I had him.
If I had just gone a little slower, I could have had him there.
That was such unfortunate.
Yeah, we learned a lot today.
That's true.
Oh, I actually wanted to play greed today.
I forgot.
Next time.
Next time we do greed.
Yeah.
What happened, Matt?
One rumor you lost in hearts.
I have no fucking clue.
I guess, in hindsight, there must have been some enemy I was supposed to kill that I just didn't see.
It's my guess.
But it was crowded as hell and shit was popping off and I was panicking.
Okay.
Middle Earth vibe?
No, this is Stronghold.
Get it right.
Maybe pause when panic, but that's cheating.
It's like pausing in a horror game when you're being chased.
That's not allowed.
You need to endure.
I'm kidding.
It's not really cheating.
I pause in speedruns to think.
Yeah, I do the same.
I do the same.
Sometimes when I see an item description, especially when they're flipping back and forth, I need to pause to read it.
Have you forgotten Bethany?
Yes.
On purpose, though.
Didn't know about this game.
Saw the earliest VOD and now that you were online.
What a difference.
What up, man?
Wishing.
You're from Denmark, I guess.
Oh, wait.
You guys are right.
I was supposed to play Bethany today.
I promised that last time.
You're right.
I forgot about that.
Didn't I tell you guys to remind me to play Bethany?
That's on you.
You didn't remind me.
Oh, you did?
Oh, shit.
What did I say to it?
Oh, I didn't see your message.
You see, I got to play.
Dude, I swear to you, I forgot I said that last time.
If I had remembered that I had said that I was going to say yes to you guys, reminding me to play Beth, I would have played that.
That's so funny.
I swear to you, I did not like intentionally throw away the promise.
You know what?
I do remember saying no to it now.
If I had remembered though, I would have said yes.
Next time we do Bethany, okay?
Bethany greed.
How about that?
I know you want Bethany and greed.
You still hate Judas now?
I do.
But I don't hate him if you get lucky.
If you get a plus one HP like I did early on, then it's good.
Then it's all good.
I mean, that's the only problem I have with him.
It's the one HP.
His damage is good.
Everything is about him is good, except the HP, right?
So if you can get that fixed early on, then you're cruising.
I love his dark arts active.
Yeah, it's really cool.
It's not something I would expect to be in this game.
I don't know why.
It feels a little weird in this game to have that.
Like it doesn't quite fit with anything else I've seen, but it works.
I mean, it's good.
Any character good, but not bad.
Exactly.
I mean, any character can be good if you have the right items, right?
Wait, what?
T word?
What T word?
Maybe don't tell me if it's a spoiler.
I don't know what it is.
Oh, which tainted carrot?
Oh, that's fine.
I think...
Well, obviously it's got to be Azazel.
Meet potential man?
That sounds like a good name for a superhero, potential man.
I own the horseman boss.
The four horsemen fell to my sword.
Bro isn't ready to see tainted squared Azazel.
I want that so bad now.
I need to get a squared Azazel.
You know what that is?
Instead of having a brimstone in one direction, it's squared, right?
So it's an area attack.
It's just a brimstone across the entire surface area of the room you're in.
That's what that is.
Of course, only the length of your attack square.
So if you get more range, you know, that'll be fun.
What about Azazel cubed?
I don't know how that would work.
I guess he would brimstone the entire floor and the next floor because it's like there's height as well, you know?
It would go across floors.
You would actually just clear every floor with one attack.
How about cubed?
Azazel just instantly teleports to the end boss.
Breaks the fourth wall.
Yeah, that type of Azazel is gonna come out of your monitor and punch you in the face.
So you need to dodge those attacks while you're playing.
Just to balance it out.
Otherwise it will be too easy.
Exactly, Fizzy Man.
I don't know the name for 5D now.
I don't either.
Is there a word for it?
Giga dimension.
I think the next game is gonna be The Sims 2.
I looked into The Sims 4 and dude, I can't stand what is happening with the DLC.
Like what on earth is going on?
That is just crazy.
Why two instead of three?
I don't know.
Maybe I'll do three.
It's just not four, you know?
Like there's... I think if you had to pay for all the DLC for Sims 4, like I would go broke.
It's so incredibly expensive.
I just sailed the seven seas to play Sims.
I can't do that, man.
I don't know how to sail.
I don't have my driver's license for the seas.
Also, I heard that Sims 4 is just not as good as Sims 2 or 3.
I mean, I've played Sims 2 very much as a child, right?
I just remember nothing.
The only thing I remember is that it was amazing.
And back then I didn't have any DLCs for it.
It was just a base game, right?
Maybe some of them I had, but yeah, it would be a whole new experience for me pretty much.
Maybe both.
We'll play both two and three, something like that.
I feel like I need something a little more relaxing next, you know?
Something to play alongside Isaac, because this is a high intensity game.
It takes a lot out of you, you know?
Like high focus.
Sims is like the opposite.
And I think with Sims, we're gonna do a chat interaction for the first time, you know?
Just sit and shoot the shit while we play Sims.
See how that goes.
Right?
Yeah.
You'll get spoiled on all the important Sims lore.
I think I'm okay.
Then we need Facecam 2, but a million subs though, on YouTube.
And then...
If I get a million subs on YouTube, I can probably afford to buy all the DLC for Sims 4, and then we go Facecam.
The music is very medieval, Wizard Bacon.
It's from Stronghold, an old RTS game that is very dear to me.
Plans for the next game?
I just mentioned it, so you just missed it.
I think I'm gonna play The Sims 2 or The Sims 3.
Maybe both.
With chat interaction.
But I was also thinking about...
Hitman, actually.
World of Assassination.
Yeah.
We'll see.
I haven't decided yet.
All Sims 4 DLC costs 2000 US dollars.
What the fuck, dude?
Even if I could afford it, at some point in my life, I would never do that just out of principle.
That's crazy.
Wow.
That is like... damn.
Damn.
I guess you would do some research on what DLCs are the most worth.
Maybe there's probably a bunch of them that you don't need, right?
Train Simulator?
Really?
That's so sad, man.
Why that one?
It's such a niche game to start with, you know?
Why punish all the people that actually want to play it?
That's crazy.
That's sad.
I don't even know what the woohoo is, Stavask.
Is it just a sim going woohoo or something?
That's disgusting, Frank.
I can't believe they do that.
That's just extortion, almost.
People are like, damn, there's not many train games out there, you know?
I want a good train game.
And then someone comes along and makes it and says, nah, nah, nah.
If you want these tracks and these trains, you got to pay up front, man.
That's just messed up.
How about Goat Simulator?
I mean, that's what we're playing right now.
Just learned game dev.
Yeah.
All right, guys, I'm gonna go now.
Next stream will maybe be Sims.
And then we're gonna keep Isaac going as well at the same time.
But it could also be a completely different game.
We'll see.
But yeah, thanks for watching.
And have a wonderful Saturday, okay?
I'll see you.
Bye bye.